Alright, Ted.
Opponents for the
finals are the Giants.
Their owner
is Henry,
so you need
to be careful.
He's really not the
type to let things go.
Relax.
I got this.
West?
Your coach's
license got revoked.
How are you even
allowed in here?
If it weren't for Ted,
I wouldn't be in
this mess
in the first place.
Luckily,
Henry pulled some
strings and paid
the right people off.
I'm the Giants'
assistant coach now.
You tried every trick
in the book
to beat Ted,
and you still lost.
Don't try to blame
him for your failure.
This time's different.
The Giants are a...
real powerhouse.
Worth over two
billion dollars.
I think that's
twenty times
the amount
of your
pathetic
team's budget?
He'll never win.